♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
["Mr. Tailor" playing]
- ♪ Fix it ♪
- ♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's settled ♪
[Ibyang] I just don't want any problems
- for your family.
- Ibyang?
I'm not your child.
[Ibyang] I'm just borrowing you
as a father.
[in English] Why don't you invite
Atoy over for dinner tonight?
[in English] A-Are you sure, Dad?
Maybe we'll have Daddy Atoy
here at home again.
Because he and Mommy
are getting back together!
[Red] Do you remember
the ivory shipment before?
It failed because of him.
I retaliated, and someone
got dragged into it.
What do you mean?
[Red] I hit-and-run Atoy's father.
[Dmitri] Why are you
only telling me this now?
I didn't know Atoy and Audrey
were connected.
[Red] Our family is doomed
if those two end up together.
[Atoy] Good evening.
Imagine, until now, I still don't know
who ran him over.
[in English] You wanna try it?
[Red] No need.
What did your father even teach you?
He was a master cutter, a tailor.
A gun is like a needle.
You can't tremble.
It always has to be precise.
Because the wrong hole ruins the fabric.
The wrong shot ruins the target.
And this is what I'll do to the one
who ran over my father.
‪PREVIOUSLY
[gunfire blasting]
[music fades]
Hey, wait!
- [Karla] What?!
- Wait, Karla!
[Billy] Are you okay?
You look like you're about
to explode with anger.
I really am angry!
[Billy] But wait.
We didn't do anything to you!
Wait. Are you friends with Eploks?
Do you know he's the child of a mistress?
No!
For me, you shouldn't judge people
because you don't know
what they're going through!
[T-Bak] Wait, wait, wait, Karla!
You!
Maybe you have a crush on Eploks,
that's why you're defending him
like that, huh?!
Don't you know his breath stinks?!
He has bad breath!
I don't like him!
What are you saying?!
It's just that Fatty is being annoying.
[T-Bak] I'm just saying.
I'm out of here!
[in English] My friend!
You get irritated so easily.
- [sneaky music playing]
- [clicks tongue]
Sir,
right now, really?
Can't it be at 2300 hours instead?
[suspicious music playing]
All right, sir.
[in English] I will be there ASAP.
- [phone blips]
- [music fades]
Daddy, sleep here instead.
Let's sleep together.
My bed is big anyway.
Um, even Mommy…
can sleep beside us.
Janine, that's not possible.
Why not?
I slept at Daddy's house.
Child, sorry.
Daddy just needs to leave.
I…
I just need to go somewhere.
Hmm?
Thank you. I'll go ahead.
Mm.
[somber music playing]
Uh, sir.
Thank you for giving me the chance to be
with my family and…
also with yours.
[in English] I'll walk him out.
[Audrey, in English] Okay, Dad.
[in English] Um, let's go, baby girl.
- Take care.
- [Janine, in English] Bye, Dad.
- [in English] Good night, Dad.
- [in English] Good night.
Uh, Atoy.
[pensive music playing]
Wh-Why?
I just want to be clear with you.
Just because I treated you well
doesn't mean you're the one
I want for my daughter.
I'm not arrogant.
But I'm honest about my standards.
I'm just being nice to you because
you're the father of my grandchild,
and that's all.
Uh, what do you mean?
[in English] You seem like a good father.
[in English] But I don't want you
around my daughter,
much more marrying her
or building a family with her.
I don't want Audrey to think
I'm separating the two of you.
[in English] But I know
what's best for her.
And it's not you.
[tense music playing]
[music fades]
[suave theme music playing]
[motorcycle revving]
- [sewing machine whirring]
- [scratches]
[snipping]
[sewing machine clacking]
- [gun cocks]
- [gunshots]
[gunshots]
[clicking]
[snipping]
[music fades]
Sir, is this sanctioned by the government?
[Mercado, in English]
I can neither confirm nor deny.
[in English] Again,
you are on a need-to-know basis.
[in English] Black ops?
[clicks tongue] Don't worry.
They'll triple your pay.
[in English] And, uh,
your mission is just
to retrieve information.
[suspicious music playing]
What information?
A terrorist group known as Obsidian
is reportedly training here
in the Philippines.
[Mercado] We don't know
the exact location.
But according to our intel,
they already have eight camps
here in the Philippines,
and we need to find them.
All of them, sir?
Your mission is to retrieve a laptop
containing the location of the camps.
We believe someone
is supporting this group.
That's why they're camping here.
We don't know who.
That's why, Atoy,
they need your help.
This is difficult, sir.
This is a national security matter, Atoy.
[in English] High-risk.
[in English] But high rewards.
[music fades]
[loud exhale]
[dramatic sting]
‪[inaudible]
[Atoy] I love you and Janine.
I want us to be whole.
[pensive music playing]
[in English] Sir, I'm sorry.
I already have a family now.
I don't want to risk that.
[in English] I'm sorry,
but I have to decline this mission.
[epic music playing]
- [clicks tongue]
- [music concludes]
Are you sure about your decision, Atoy?
Sir, my situation is different now.
With all due respect.
I already have a child.
My priority now is my family.
[pensive music playing]
Before, I put the country first.
But, sir, I'm no longer in service.
[inhales]
I know… [sighs]
this mission I'm giving you is difficult.
But I hope that now
I can talk
to the soldier I used to rely on.
There must be someone else
who can do this mission, sir.
Let them do it.
[in English] But you're
my best tracker, Atoy.
I know you don't want
to leave your family.
But what if those terrorists start moving?
What about the families
that will be destroyed?
The mothers, fathers, and children
who will be victimized, or worse,
killed because we didn't act immediately?
[tense music playing]
Atoy.
[in English] Doing this for your country
is also a service to your family.
[music fades]
- [crickets chirping]
- [clicks tongue]
[in English] Thanks, Dad.
[smirks]
That Atoy really expects
you'll give him and Audrey your blessing.
He's an idiot to think
we'll let them be together.
[sighs]
Audrey will eventually find out
what I did.
[in English] I just hope…
- [pensive music playing]
- [inhales]
that I won't regret my decision.
I can clearly see the joy on her face.
There's nothing I can do, Dad.
I didn't mean for it to happen.
You should have finished off--
You should have finished off
that Atoy long ago,
so I wouldn't be worrying now!
You keep giving me problems, Red!
[music fades]
[in English] Let me correct my mistake.
[in English] I can kill him now.
[tense music playing]
And what?
Let my grandchild grow up
without a father?!
And don't you realize?
If something happens to Atoy,
we'll be the first suspects
because I kept him away from Audrey!
[in English] Let me remind you.
[ominous music playing]
Pray that he doesn't discover
what you did to his father.
Or better yet,
prepare yourself for that day.
[tense music playing]
[music fades]
What is this?
[Atoy] "Fortishell"?
Isn't that where we get
our hard-shell cases for our equipment?
Yes.
Their products are high-quality
and military-grade.
Where can I get one of these?
[suspicious music playing]
[Mercado] It's not commercially available.
But I know
the only office distributor here.
[tense music playing]
[wind chimes clinking]
[Atoy] 'Nang!
Oh, you're still here?
Ah.
I just finished an order.
I'm heading home soon.
You close up, okay?
How's Ibyang?
They're fine.
Don't worry.
The child is just fretting about you.
You know Ibyang. She'll miss you too.
Just wait. She'll be the one
to come to you.
Ah.
How was your dinner with Audrey's family?
[pensive music playing]
Her father talked to me.
He doesn't want Audrey and me
to get back together.
What about your child?
Well,
I'll still continue being a father.
That's fine with him.
[melancholic music playing]
But when it comes to Audrey…
He really doesn't want it.
He doesn't want us to be together.
[Cita] Oh?
Didn't Audrey object?
[Atoy] She doesn't know, Godmother.
She doesn't know yet.
[heavy sigh]
I don't know how to tell her.
Don't worry.
Whether you and Audrey
end up together or not,
Karla and I are here as your family.
You know, honestly,
I feel uneasy about Audrey's family.
Hmm. Didn't you say Red is a bad person?
It's like he's seething inside.
So, maybe
he's just like his father?
[suspicious music playing]
[Mercado on the phone]
Padua, have you left
the Fortishell office?
Yes, sir. Uh, sorry.
I just got to reply now.
The signal inside was weak.
Did you get my message?
I'll send you now
the screenshot of the unit itself,
the receipt, and the order number.
[in English] Sir, it's confirmed.
[in English] The laptop unit was sold to
and is registered
under the Zahran Embassy.
[Mercado, in English] Good job, Atoy.
I agree it's possible the laptop we're
looking for is at the Zahran Embassy.
[in English] That's why I immediately
ordered a hack on their system.
[Mercado] The IT team checked the emails,
and the ambassador has scheduled events.
One of which
is a meeting with expat businessmen here.
[in English] Copy, sir.
[music fades]
I know what to do.
[Mercado, in English]
I will send you some files
of the attendees of that meeting.
[tense music plays, stops]
[in English] Hey, Atoy! What's up, man?
Oh!
It seems like you're thinking
about some deep stuff, huh?
[in English] Is, uh, everything okay?
Oh.
Seems not, huh?
[in English] How can I help you?
[in English] Anything at all.
[in English] Anything?
[in English] Anything.
[sneaky music playing]
Are you sure, anything?
All right, game.
You really want to help me?
[in English] Anything.
[music fades]
[in English] Sir Atoy.
I'm gonna do my best.
Because I don't want you
to fail your mission.
Thanks. Wait. Take off your towel.
- Ah, yes. Okay, okay.
- Our measurement isn't accurate.
- [sighs]
- There.
Actually, I'm kind of excited.
But, you know, also nervous.
But kind of just right. It's like, uh,
maybe 10% nervous and…
90% excited.
No. No, no, no.
That's wrong, that's wrong.
It's like, reversed. It's…
90% nervous and then 10% excited.
[in English] It's-- No, no, no.
That's no-- It's not right.
It's like-- I can't explain.
[in English] It's, um… Uh…
- Oh! Can--
- There, lower your hand.
Can I vlog this?
[music fades]
[in English] Of course not. No, of course.
[in English] It's-- It's a secret mission,
Brother Kurt, come on!
Sorry. That's a stupid question.
[sharp exhale]
[sneaky music playing]
Okay. What you need to do is simple.
Don't worry.
Just listen to my instructions.
- Yes.
- [in English] It will be fine.
- [in English] Okay. Yes.
- Okay? But…
it would help more
if you knew some Russian words
or Russian phrases.
- Ah, Russian?
- Yes, Russian.
- [in English] Russian?
- Mm-hmm.
Oh-- Russian, uh-- Not really.
[in English] I-I know a little Ilocano.
[in English] And then, uh,
I'm very good at American English,
of course, but…
I'll-- I'll learn.
I'll learn. I'll research, so…
so I won't embarrass myself with you.
- [in English] Research, huh? I like that.
- Yes.
- [in English] Initiative.
- [in English] Yes.
God bless.
- Ah. I love you.
- [chuckles]
[phone vibrating]
- [in English] Excuse me.
- [huffs] Okay.
[phone vibrating]
[in English] Hello, sir!
[clicks tongue, in English]
Doing good, sir.
[soft rock music playing]
[Atoy] I found my brother…
Andrei Sokolov.
I know your skills
aren't limited to tracking, Atoy.
You know a lot about gadgets and guns.
[Mercado] But the most impressive of all…
You're like a chameleon.
[in English] You can be anyone.
That's why I trust you so much, Atoy.
[Atoy, in English] I will do my best, sir.
[music fades]
[rock music playing]
[Mercado on the phone]
You don't just copy appearances.
Even the personalities
and characteristics,
you capture them.
That's why you're needed for this mission.
[in English] Good luck, Atoy.
- [guard, in English] Morning, sir.
- [Kurt, in English] Good morning.
[Mercado on the phone]
Since we now have access to the computer
of the ambassador's secretary…
[device blips]
…the name of an expat
was added to the list,
who is in the business
of selling textiles, etc.
[in English] How can I help you, sir?
[Mercado, in English]
And that's you, Atoy.
- [in English] You will be known as…
- Sokolov.
Mr. Alexei Sokolov.
[in English] My brother, Andrei.
Andrei Sokolov.
- [computer blips]
- [in English] I'm sorry, sir.
[in English] But on my list,
it shows that you declined the invitation.
[in English] Oh, right.
[in English] Right, right. Uh, but, um…
[in English] We… We changed
our mind last minute.
[in English] C-Can you check
your email again?
[mutters]
[music fades]
[computer blipping]
[in English] You're correct, sir.
[in English] Our apologies
for not updating our list.
[in English] No worries.
[in English] Here are your access cards.
[rock music playing]
[in English] Thank you.
[device blips]
[suspicious music playing]
[elevator dings]
[in English] Sir, your badge?
Sir, you don't have access here.
Ah, sorry. I thought
this was the 12th floor.
[device blipping]
[music swells]
[Samir, in English] Excuse me.
[in English] Stop!
[tense music playing]
[in English] What is your name?
‪[dramatic stinging]
[in English] I am, uh, Alexei Sokolov.
[music fades]
- [in English] You. What is your name?
- [in English] Uh, Kurt--
[Atoy clears throat, then coughs]
Teous.
[in English] Uh,
very courteous staff here.
[Kurt, in English] I am Andrei Sokolov.
[in English] We are the Sokolov brothers.
[in English] You are brothers?
Uh-huh.
- [in English] You two?
- [Atoy] Mm-hmm.
[rousing music playing]
[electronic blipping]
[tense music playing]
[man 1, in English]
You're here for the meeting?
[in English] What business are you into?
[clicks tongue, in English] Textiles.
[in English] The ambassador
will see you now. Please come with me.
[muttering]
Atoy, Atoy, your neck!
I know this.
Atoy is pretending to be pregnant.
He should have just brought me along.
I could have been his assistant there.
Atoy might mess up.
[Mercado, in English] Oh, you found it!
That's our target.
[Mercado] If you have the chance
to get it now, do it.
[in English] But make sure
you won't be compromised.
[Samir] Hey!
[in English] What are you doing here?
‪UP NEXT
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
Uh…
♪ One cut, and it's settled ♪
♪ Fix it ♪
Subtitle translation by: Rachel C. Arias